[theme music playing]
I want you to cancel everything.
-Congressman…
-Shut up!
[chanting] Take them down!
Bring down the Ardientes!
[Emilia] Now then, tell me
everything there is to know
about the woman we know as Ivy Aguas.
-For a new Ardiente!
No!
Make that bastard suffer!
I want Diego Torillo's head!
Who are you really? Are you Lily Cruz?!
I am Lily Cruz!
Now that I'm here, I will
have you buried alive too!
[Julio] You need to break up
with Ivy Aguas.
Or else, you will lose this election.
You forget that I'm an Ardiente!
I'm a predator.
Or a kitten pretending to be a lion.
Anna, go back home.
I won't let them do to you
what they did to Nanny Carlotta.
You're leaving, Anna.
-[screaming]
-What's wrong with you?
Lily Cruz is back!
She's alive! With whom, Papa? Madrigal!
I'm glad to see you again, Jepoy.
I promised you I wouldn't leave
no matter what, didn't I?
I need to stay alive to protect you.
Ivy Aguas was adopted.
She must be the real Lily Cruz
because she's been
hiding her real identity!
When will you leave Ivy alone?
The enemy is using
elementary tactics on us!
Divide and conquer!
Blood is thicker than water!
[Ivy] Nanny, you have visitors.
Nanny, please help me convince them
not to push through with their plans.
[sobbing]
You don't have to carry it all.
She was our family too.
I know, Jepoy.
And she always will be.
I understand how you both feel,
but please try to understand me too.
I already made up my mind.
You and Anna will go overseas
as soon as possible.
Haven't you heard
anything we've said, Ivy?
We're not leaving.
Anna, this is my fight.
You mean, our fight. We all want justice.
This is our fight.
Anna, please listen to me.
Please stop being so stubborn.
Ivy, you don't have to protect me.
I can take care of myself.
I learned from you, remember?
You taught me how to fight for life.
Aunt Carlotta let us experience
a mother's love,
even though we were all orphans.
Ivy, this fight isn't
yours alone. It's ours.
Anna, listen to me.
Anything but this fight.
I'd gladly ask for your help,
but not in this one.
Want to know why?
You don't understand
how hard it was for me…
when Nanny Carlotta died.
It was my fault.
She died because of me.
You lost someone dear to you
because of me.
So, if you won't listen to me,
I might lose you two.
I don't want that to happen
because I care about you, Anna.
So, please listen to what I say.
Ivy, you know how the Ardientes
tortured me before,
and Anna saw the scars from it.
We also hold a grudge
against the Ardientes.
That's my point!
Jepoy, that's what I'm trying to say.
I can't even imagine--
Knowing what you experienced,
how Anna saw the scars…
And yet, here you are!
You even brought Anna here.
Do you want her to
experience the same fate?
As much as possible,
I don't want anyone else
to make sacrifices for me.
I don't want anyone
to get involved in this.
I can't bear it anymore!
My conscience can no longer take it.
So many people have been killed and hurt.
Now you want to involve Anna too?
So you two will listen to me.
I won't deny the justice you're
seeking for Nanny Carlotta.
You mean so much to me,
so you have to leave as soon as possible.
[tense music playing]
[Julio] You need to break up
with Ivy Aguas.
Or else, you will lose this election.
You forget that I'm an Ardiente!
I may love Ivy,
but I never forget who I am.
I'm a predator.
A predator?
Or a kitten pretending to be a lion?
I found out from my private investigator
that Ivy Aguas was adopted.
So, she must be the real Lily Cruz
because she's been
hiding her real identity!
When will you leave Ivy alone?
No, Arnaldo.
I will never let her become an Ardiente.
Because she has so many secrets,
and, until I uncover them all,
I won't leave that woman alone!
HON, WHERE ARE YOU? I NEED YOU.
ANSWER THE PHONE.
WHERE ARE YOU? I'LL FIND YOU
WHEREVER THE HELL YOU ARE!
We're not leaving, Ivy.
We won't leave you!
[tense music playing]
[phone chimes]
WHERE ARE YOU? I'LL FIND YOU
WHEREVER THE HELL YOU ARE!
You're so stubborn.
I need to go.
-Ivy, wait! Where--
-Do you know what you did?
Now that you revealed Anna as Lily Cruz,
I need to rush the wedding!
Let's go.
[ominous music playing]
Hon?
Where have you been?
We were together at the plaza
earlier, but you disappeared.
Yes, didn't your mom tell you
that we were together?
And Lily Cruz finally showed up.
Lily Cruz, yes.
I'm glad you mentioned that.
I'm curious, what do you think about that?
Shocked.
But at the same time,
I can breathe easily now
because your mom won't doubt me anymore.
Your family will stop thinking
that I'm Lily Cruz.
[scoffs]
You know what's funny?
Mom mentioned that, because you
didn't tell us you were adopted,
there's a possibility
that you could be Lily Cruz.
Hon, it's too personal for me.
But, since I am your fiancée,
and we're going to be married…
Yes, hon.
I'm adopted.
Prianka Aguas adopted me.
She fed me, clothed me,
and sent me to school.
She took in a hopeless stray.
Now, here I am.
My name is Ivy Aguas, and I'm adopted.
Well, I was surprised
you'd react that way.
[unsettling music playing]
I'm just happy. I know you better now.
"Diego Torillo:
Savior of Poblacion Ardiente!"
Batch!
You're featured on a national broadsheet!
It really pays to be inspired!
Thanks again for all your help.
Don't mention it.
Batch, let me ask you.
Aside from running for office,
is there something else that inspires you?
[scoffs]
[chuckles]
There is, isn't there?
Is it long-distance?
I haven't seen you with anyone.
Or, are you still hung up on Lily Cruz?
You've been crazy about her since college!
So, it's still her?
Or, has Ivy Aguas taken her place?
Don't be silly.
We have things to do. Let's go. Come on!
Well, Arnaldo, congratulations!
You finally made it to the front page.
Your disgrace is now a national joke!
Any ideas how we can get out of it?
No idea.
Like you said, I'm bound to lose.
So, why even try?
Hon.
[Julio] Emilia…
Do you have any brilliant ideas?
Honestly, Papa,
there's nothing I can do to
help your exceptional grandson.
[Julio chuckles]
Well, the only thing
I can think of right now, Papa, is…
I really believe that Lily Cruz
is financing Diego's campaign.
They're using her money
to fund the campaign,
and we have to cut them off.
So, um…
I'd like to take this opportunity
to say sorry to you, Ivy.
For thinking that you were
Lily Cruz all along.
I sincerely apologize.
Of course, Emilia.
Apology accepted.
Thank you. So, does that mean
we can both join forces
to finally end Lily Cruz?
[tense music playing]
Gentlemen, I brought some refreshments.
I'll put this over there.
-Okay.
-Let's take a break.
-All right.
Nanny! Uncle!
Nanny, what's wrong?
Some people arrived from Manila.
More enemies?
What did the Ardientes do this time?
No, it's not like that.
They're suppliers for the "royal wedding."
It seems like Arnaldo and Ivy
are rushing to get married.
They're going to join forces.
I don't get it. What's her agenda?
What does Ivy Aguas want from us?
[unsettling music playing]
[knocking on door]
Congressman, you have a visitor.
Thank you.
-Hi, Congressman.
-Come in, Doctor!
Well…
If you came all the way here
to tell me the results of my biopsy…
you must be the bearer of bad news.
Julio, I'm sorry,
but your cancer is back.
[dramatic music playing]
[sighs]
I did tell you before that
there was a chance
for your cancer to recur.
Even after your remission back in the U.S.
But with your recent accident…
We all know that bone cancer
is very dangerous.
Doc.
Are you saying my days are numbered?
Are we talking years?
Months?
Weeks?
Julio, we have to conduct more tests.
Oh!
Well, then…
I think it's best if we
postpone this talk.
With the kind of news that you have…
I have a lot of things
to put into order in my life.
Excuse me, then.
Of course.
Well…
If I have to die…
I need to make sure
that the Ardientes will stay in power.
Arnaldo's wedding has to push through.
Because he will need Ivy Aguas.
When Arnaldo and Ivy's wedding
pushes through,
the Ardientes will become invincible.
They will gain more power and wealth,
and they will continue
to bring terror to this town.
Trust me, Nanny.
I will do everything
to stop their wedding.
I still don't agree
with any of your plans.
But since you're persistent,
this is what we'll do.
On the day of my wedding,
I want you gone from Poblacion Ardiente.
Are you serious, Ivy?
Why will you marry that monster?
He killed Aunt Carlotta!
Anna.
I know what I'm doing.
That's my plan. It's one way for us
to seek justice for Nanny Carlotta.
So, you need to trust my plans.
There will be no wedding, Ivy.
I won't let you marry that murderer!
If I have to sleep with the devil himself
to avenge Nanny Carlotta, I will!
Don't try to stop my wedding
or any of my plans.
Don't you dare.
Like what I've been telling you,
you have to trust my plans.
The last time I saw you
like this was when Mom lost.
It only goes to show that
you're worried I'll lose too.
Yes.
Come on, Arnaldo.
Don't give me that questioning look.
Don't give me that surprised look.
Because you know I'm right!
You allowed your emotions
to rule over that thick head of yours.
Well, partly…
Partly, I'm also to blame.
Partly, it is my fault!
You know why? I've loved you too
much as my grandson.
I allowed my emotions to rule me too.
How--
How dumb could I get?!
You know what? I should've
given you a good beating
every time you failed in the past.
How could I forget? These are my rules!
How could I forget that a tiger,
no matter how ferocious,
can turn into a tame kitten
when you feed it with milk
instead of fresh meat,
and when you take care of it too much?!
That tiger turned into a kitten!
[Arnaldo] Hey!
I'm not weak.
You're helpless!
[emphatic] You are helpless!
You're like a dying puppy!
You know what that looks like?
The truth of the matter is,
-Diego is far better than you!
-Take back what you said!
I said take it back! Take it back!
[tense music playing]
[laughs]
Look at yourself.
You've become uncontrollable.
The once calculating,
intelligent, brave grandson
that I had is gone.
What's left is a childish
and spoiled weakling.
A sensitive little boy.
[yells and smacks]
Get your act together!
Let it bleed! Bleed!
Bleed and taste your blood!
Because I'm telling you,
you are going to bleed more
than you would want.
You will bleed far worse
if you're going to lead Ardiente.
Arnaldo, Ardiente is yours for the taking!
I will leave this family in your hands.
Poblacion Ardiente is yours!
But you will have to want it.
You will have to crave it.
You will have to fight tooth,
nail, and claw to own it!
You have to love it!
Love it more than life itself!
Love it more than Ivy Aguas!
More than anything else!
Do you understand?
-Yes.
-Do you?! Do you understand?!
Yes! Yes!
-I can't hear you!
-Yes, I understand!
-What?!
-Yes, I understand! Yes!
Yes, I understand! Yes!
Now, let me ask you.
If I made you choose between
Ardiente and Ivy Aguas,
which will you choose?! Answer me!
-Ardiente!
-Answer me!
Ardiente!
I will kill everyone even Ivy Aguas!
When it comes to Poblacion Ardiente!
There! There! That is the power!
That is the look that I want from you!
I want you to be mad! Mad!
Mad for power!
Not for stupid love!
[dramatic music playing]
We've managed to sway
60 percent of Ardiente.
And our next target is this.
Their bailiwick.
I know it will be hard,
but I know we can do it.
Of course, Batch! We can do this!
Especially now that
more people believe in you.
They want to support Team Diego!
They believe in him because
he's handsome and brave!
Oh, well! He got that from me!
[laughing]
-Am I right?
-Pandoy, you're just hungry!
[laughing]
Come on, let's eat! Aunt Camia, let's go.
-Let's go!
-Yeah, Diego!
[phone rings]
Hello, Lily?
Mom, we need to meet.
I need you and Diego.
Are you all right? Did something happen?
[Ivy] I'm okay.
It's a long story.
I'll tell you when we meet.
I'll text you the address.
Okay. Diego and I
will be there right away.
Thank you, Mom.
Auntie, is there a problem?
Diego, it's Lily.
She said she needs to see us.
We need to meet her now.
Okay, Auntie.
Nanny, Uncle we need to go.
-Batch, you're in charge.
-Okay.
-We really need to go.
-Help yourselves.
-Bye, Nanny.
-[Marlon] Take care.
How can I be so dumb?
Grandpa, I-- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for everything I've done.
No, no, no. That's okay.
That's water under the bridge.
Now, we start anew.
Now, we become methodical and cunning.
We will first remove all the obstacles.
We will eliminate everything in your way.
Okay, well…
Does that mean my wedding's canceled?
No, no, no, no, no!
The wedding goes as planned!
Arnaldo, once you've become the governor,
you'll need a first lady.
And Ivy Aguas fits that role to a tee.
Now, I don't care if you
treat her like some goddess
or a piece of garbage after the wedding.
What's important is
for her money to become ours.
[Julio sighs]
Now…
when this is all done…
our next move is to
make sure of your victory.
All right.
Well, then… I'll take care of Diego.
I'll kill them all.
Diego, Camia Cruz, Lily Cruz, Madrigal.
I'd gladly kill them all.
-No, no, no. No, Arnaldo.
-There won't be anyone left--
You leave the dirty jobs to me.
I will handle this.
I want you to focus on your campaign…
and on your upcoming wedding.
Rush everything. Rush the preparation.
Push everything! Push them forward.
Make them move to complete this wedding.
I'd be mad to think that
it's just a coincidence
that Lily Cruz was there
when I cornered Ivy Aguas!
I don't believe that. They can't fool me.
Don't complicate things, Emilia.
You already made up with Ivy
in front of Julio and Arnaldo.
Please don't make yourself
look stupid again.
Auntie, I'm going to hunt down Lily Cruz.
If I have to kidnap and torture her
until she tells me the truth, I'll do it.
And I know someone who can do that for me.
[scoffs] Oh, please.
Leave me out of this mess.
I don't want to become
involved in your dirty jobs.
-Are you sure, Raul?
-Of course.
What if I ask for Jaguar's help instead?
You know he's crazy for me.
He will do anything for me.
[scoffs] What are you saying?
Why are you talking about Jaguar?
Are you trying to make me jealous?
Come on, Emilia.
If you're just trying to
make me jealous, it's fine.
I just don't want to see you together.
You wouldn't like to
see me jealous. All right?
[giggles]
It's such a good feeling
that you're being desired
not just by one but two.
[chuckles]
Emilia…
Grandpa, I promise.
I'll make the most out of this.
[stammers] I swear.
Thank you.
Thank you, Arnaldo.
You know…
I am…
I am getting old, Arnaldo.
I can feel my candle…
melting.
I can sense the light
in my eyes growing dim.
And the last thing I'd like
to see before I close my eyes…
is you standing and lording it
over Poblacion Ardiente…
continuing my legacy.
That is my dream.
I-- I don't get it.
Why are you talking like that, Grandpa?
-[thud]
-Arnaldo, it is what it is!
Everybody dies!
The time will come that I will die.
Remember once upon a time when I told you…
that I will live forever?
Arnaldo.
You are my life!
It is through you
that I will live forever!
In my dream…
you will be the king
of Poblacion Ardiente!
And running in your veins
is the Ardiente blood.
And it will be as if I am with you,
that I'm standing there,
and still leading you,
and still ruling Poblacion Ardiente.
Make my dream come true, Arnaldo.
Make my dream come true before I fade.
[emotional music playing]
Viva Ardiente.
[ominous music playing]
Viva Ardiente!
-Mom.
-Lily.
-Diego.
-What happened to you?
Nothing, Mom. I'm fine.
But Emilia almost found out
my real identity.
What?!
It's a good thing you got out of it.
Someone helped me.
Who?
[Jepoy] Me.
Mom, they're the ones who helped me.
This is Anna.
She's our childhood friend.
Anna was the one who pretended to be me.
She pretended to be Lily Cruz.
[dramatic music playing]
Don't proceed, Emilia. Please!
Stop the obsession.
[scoffs] Auntie, did I just
hear you say stop?
And you think that's part
of my vocabulary? "Stop"?
What Emilia wants, Emilia gets.
And I'm sure he can't resist me.
[unsettling music playing]
[phone rings]
Hello, Jaguar.
Did you miss me, sweetheart?
Because I missed you.
The scent of your neck,
and the smooth touch of your hands.
You taste so good.
[giggling]
Can you stop flirting
with me, Jaguar? Enough.
I want you to do something for me.
I have a job for you.
It's my enemy, Lily Cruz.
[Jaguar] I'm not your servant, Emilia.
Yes, but you need something from me.
You want me to join you.
So, if you do this, I'll be yours.
[chuckles]
Even if you don't choose me,
Emilia, it won't matter.
First of all,
your family, the Ardientes,
is about to go down.
That's why I'm better off
siding with Diego Torillo.
But because I like you,
I'll give you another chance.
Make your decision as soon as possible.
Before it's too late, Emilia.
Jaguar, I'll make this easy for you.
Leave the Ardientes alone.
Leave. Hide, and hide carefully.
Because when I put this phone down,
your death toll will start to ring.
I will be coming for you,
and I'll be bringing
the fires of hell with me.
I promise you, Jaguar.
I will put an end to your life.
This is too much.
I don't like this.
Lily…
It's time to stop pretending.
You're just making everything
more complicated.
I agreed to let you marry Arnaldo
so that you could carry out your plans.
Even though I hated the idea,
I let you do it because I trust you.
But this?
If Emilia exposed you, then you
should've revealed yourself.
We'll face this together.
Our forces are stronger now.
We can take them on.
You don't need a fake Lily Cruz.
[dramatic music playing]
Stop dealing with Jaguar.
You gained nothing from him.
Instead of you making a fool out of him,
it's been the other way around.
It's so hard to tame him, Papa.
-I need time!
-I don't have the time, Emilia.
And I'm tired of you
sabotaging our family.
From now on,
I forbid you to act on your own.
everything that you'll do
will come directly from me.
You will follow me, just like before.
Now let me lay down some rules
that have to be followed.
First of all, stop pestering Ivy Aguas.
Stop thwarting her wedding plans
with your son.
And another thing.
You will genuinely make peace with her.
Kneel before her if necessary.
Kiss her feet if you have to!
In short…
You will do everything to please her.
[gasps] I can't do that.
I'm not going to do that, Papa.
She's the one marrying into our family.
She's the one who's supposed
to be adjusting to me,
not the other way around!
With all due respect,
Ivy had no idea about
what Jepoy and I did.
It was our decision, because, like you,
we also seek justice
for Aunt Carlotta's death.
You knew Nanny Carlotta?
I'm her niece.
She was like a mother to me.
Mom…
Like you, I don't agree
with their plans either.
But they kept on insisting.
They said they have to do it
for Nanny Carlotta.
That's why they want to fight
against the Ardientes.
I'm just scared, Lily.
So many people have been
dragged into this mess.
At this point, the Ardientes
might soon find out
who you really are and hurt you.
Too much innocent blood has been shed.
We came here prepared.
Anna even studied everything.
I know Lily Cruz in and out.
I know everything
about her and her family.
Everything the Ardientes put her through.
Thank you.
I know you just want to help.
But this is too much.
For a mother like me, it's hard to accept
that someone is pretending
to be my daughter.
Excuse me.
Disobey my rules, Emilia,
and you will regret it
for the rest of your life.
-[sighs]
-But if you follow my orders,
I promise you,
you will be rewarded generously.
[sighs] My dear daughter.
Let's be close to each other once again.
You need me.
I need you.
This family needs you.
Okay, Papa. What do you want me to do?
Lily Cruz.
[ominous music playing]
[Arnaldo] From now on,
I don't want lazy and incompetent people
in my campaign team.
I need people who will do
everything to make me win.
Now, if you're not that person…
you can stand up and get out of my sight.
[tense music playing]
-You.
-Yes, me.
You're going to lose this election.
Isn't that right? Admit it.
Stand up, and let's leave
this worthless politician.
Are you done?
I'm leaving.
Wait! Just a second.
You're leaving without your paycheck?
[sighs] Hold on.
-[smacks]
-[groaning]
[coughing]
-[smacks]
-[groaning]
-[coughs]
-[Arnaldo] So…
Who else is going to stand up and leave?
Anyone?
Answer me!
Well then, let's begin.
[unsettling music playing]
Mom…
I tried to talk to them.
I told them I was against their plans.
So…
Mom.
[sobbing]
Please don't cry.
I promise you that Anna and Jepoy
won't be here for long.
I just have to regain
the trust of the Ardientes.
I can't reveal who I am just yet
because I have to push through
with my wedding to Arnaldo.
Mom, I know this is hard for you.
Please stop crying, Mom.
I know it's difficult,
but you have to trust me.
Lily, how can I trust you?
You keep secrets from me.
Mom, I hate having
to keep secrets from you.
But I have to prioritize
your safety above all.
What about yours?
Are you safe with the things you're doing?
I can't let something bad happen to you.
You managed to convince Ivy?
Diego.
Thank you for watching over Ivy
when I wasn't around.
Jepoy, as long as I'm alive,
I'll keep protecting her.
[tense music playing]
Are Ivy and her mom going to be okay?
They're fighting because of me.
No, it was my fault.
Don't worry.
They just have to talk it over.
You're Diego, aren't you?
Lily's childhood best friend.
If you need to know more
about our childhood,
just ask me about it.
If you're pretending to be Lily Cruz,
you need to learn everything about her.
[Jepoy] Hold on.
You don't want Ivy to
marry Arnaldo either, right?
You already know my answer to that.
[tense music playing]
This is a peace agreement.
From this day on, the killing, cheating,
and blackmailing between Diego Torillo
and Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo will stop.
[Arnaldo] For a peaceful election.
[cheering]
Ladies and gentlemen, Lily Cruz!
[reporter] Do you also
plan to file a lawsuit
against the Ardientes
like your mother did?
[Emilia] I want you to witness
Lily Cruz being buried alive.
It's just one phone call away.
[theme music playing]